Guide to the School of Management, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1997-2000; Accession 2013-A-074
  - Grade reports
    - Grade Reports: MGT 840 International Financial Reporting, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 870 Fundamentals of Accounting, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 871 Financial Reporting, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 880 Strategic Environment of Management, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 885 Foundations of Teams, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 890 Valuation and Investment, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 992 Strategy and Policy in Health Care Sector, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 993 National Innovation Systems, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Grade Reports: Non-SOM Courses, 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Grade Reports: Miscellaneous, Course Checklist, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 515 Decision Analysis and Game Theory, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 521 Macroeconomic Analysis, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 523 Managerial Negotiating, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 525 Competitive Strategies, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 526 Regulation and Strategy in Telecommunications, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 527 Strategic Management of Nonprofit Organizations, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 529 Practice and Management of Creativity and Innovation, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 538 Managing Strategic Change, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 541 Corporate Finance, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 542 International Finance, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 543 Financial Instruments and Contracts, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 544 Investment Management, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 547 Fixed Income Security Analysis, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 556 Designing and Implementing Global Strategies, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 557 Product Planning and Development, 1999 Spr (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 571 Operations Management I, 1999 Spr (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 574 Management of Quality, 1999 Spr (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 580 Business, Governmentt and International Economy, 1999 Spr (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 529 Redesigning Organizations: A Computational View, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 594 Emerging Markets of Latin America, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 616 Financial Derivatves and Risk Management, 1999 Spr (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 618 and 619 Entrepreneurship, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 633 Strategic Human Resource Management, 1999 Spr (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 635 Venture Capital, 1999 Spr (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 645 Foreign Exchange and Related Derivative Instruments, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 646 Financial Institutions, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 659 Transportation and the Environment, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 668 Field Studies in Strategy, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 673 International Strategy and Competition, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 675 Business and Regulation in the TV Industry, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 690 and 691 Independent Reading and Research, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 694 Housing and Community Development, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 695 Nonprofit Organizations Clinic, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 696 Introduction to Planning and Development, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 740 Financial Economics I, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 802 Internet Strategy and Marketing, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 803 Leadership, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 804 Marketing of Financial Services, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 805 Service Management, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 806 Supply Chain Management, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 807 Mutual Funds, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 812 Financial Statement Analysis, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 813 Advanced Financial Statement Analysis, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 815 Managerial Accounting, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 816 Advanced Managerial Accounting, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 818 Advanced Financial Reporting, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 827 Institutional Funds Management, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 829 Practice of Real Estate Development, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 833 Organizational Communication and Influence, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 836 Program Evaluation, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 839 Active Investing, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 840 International Financial Reporting, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 841 Private Equity Investing, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 849 Real Estate Finance for Institutional…, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 869 Integrative Management, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 881 Politics of Strategic Management, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 886 Designing and Managing Organizations, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 891 Corporate Finance and Options, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 985 Professionalism Under Pressure in Law and Medicine, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 994 Strategy, Government, and Management of a Large PublicCorporation, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 996 SynThesis; Non-SOM courses, 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Grade Reports: Miscellaneous, Course Checklist, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 510 Data Analysis and Statistics, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 520 Economic Analysis, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 521 Macroeconomic Analysis, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 525 Competitive Strategies, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 541 Corporate Finance, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 542 International Finance, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 543 Instruments and Contracts, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 544 Investment Management, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 546 International Financial Markets, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 547 Fixed Income Security Analysis, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 551 Internet Strategy and Marketing, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 555 Pricing Strategy, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 558 Consumer Behavior, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 559 Marketing Strategy, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 578 China as an Emerging Market, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 585 Operating Systems, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 586 Strategy, Technology and War, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 589 Information Technology for Management, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 593 Global Financial Reform, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 611 Policy Modeling, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 618 Entrepreneurship, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 567 Entrepreneurship, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 621 Theory and History of Money, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 635 Venture Capital and Private Equity Investments, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 690 and 691 Independent Reading and Research, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 692 Business Ethics, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 695 Nonprofit Organizations Clinic, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 696 Introduction to Planning and Development, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 806 Supply Chain Management, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 808 Introduction to Operations Research, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 809 Leading Strategic Change, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 812 Financial Statement Analysis, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 813 Advanced Financial Statement Analysis, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 814 Financial Statements/Nonprofit Organizations, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 816 Advanced Managerial Accounting, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 831 Valuation of Technology, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 840 International Financial Analysis and Equity Valuation, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 841 Private Equity Investing, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 861 Management of Computational Assets, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 868 Extreme Variability in Prices, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 870 Fundamentals of Accounting, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 880 The Strategic Environment of Management, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 885 Foundation of Teams, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 890 Valuation and Investment, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 994 Strategy, Governance and Management of Public Corporations, 1999 Fall (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Grade Reports: Non-SOM courses, 2000 Fall (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Grade Reports: General Information, Course Checklist, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 515 (all sections) Decision Analysis and Game Theory, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Grade Reports: MGT521 (all sections) Macroeconomic Analysis, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 522 MicroEconApplications: PubSectr, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 523 Advanced Managerial Negotiating, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 525 Competitive Strategies, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 526 Corporate Strategies/Telecommunications, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 527 Strategic Management of Nonprofit Organizations, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 541 Corporate Finance, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 542 International Finance, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 543 Instruments and Contracts, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 544 Investment Management, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 545 Financial Engineering, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 547 Fixed Income Security Analysis, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 550 Marketing Management, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 557 Product Planning and Development, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 571 Operations Management, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 572 Operations Management II, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 574 Management of Quality, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 579 Managing Risks in Foreign Markets, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 588 Information Technology and Corporate Strategy, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 594 Emerging Markets of Latin America, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 633 Strategic Human Resources Management, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 635 Venture Capital and Private Equity, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 640 Numerical Methods in Option Pricing, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 641 Behavioral Finance, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 644 Structured Finance, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 647 Cases in Entrepreneurial Finance, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 648 Fixed Income Trading and Investment Strategies, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 668 Field Studies in Strategy, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 673 International Strategy and Competition, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 675 Law, Business and Regulation in TV, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 690 – Sections 01, 03, 04, 05, 06, 07, 08, 10 Independent Studies, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 697 Intermediate Planning and Development, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 803 Leadership, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 804 Marketing of Financial Services, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 807 Antitrust Law and Business Mgr, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 812 Financial Statement Analysis, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 815 Managerial Accounting, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 818 Advanced Financial Reporting, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 820 Foreign Exchange and Related Derivative Instruments, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 822 How to Start a High Tech Company, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 827 Institutional Funds Management, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 829 Practice of Real Estate Development, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 833 Organizational Communications and Influence, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 837 Quantifying Customer Preferences, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 838 Applied Regression Analysis, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 839 Active Investing, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 840 International Financial Analysis, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 816 Advanced Managerial Accounting, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 842 Financial Policy/Emerging Market Nations, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 849 RealEstate/Institutional Investors, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 860 Challenges/Opportunities of Global Lead, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 862 Applied Urban Public Finance, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 863 Life Sciences Business, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 865 Cuba, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 871 Financial Reporting, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 872 Strategic Financial Decision Lab I, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 881 Politics of Strategic Management, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 886 Managing and Designing Organizations, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 887 Essentials/Managerial Negotiat, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 891 Corporate Finance and Options, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 984 Studies in Grand Strategy, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 996 SynThesis, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Grade Reports: MGT 998 Strategy/Health Care Industry, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Grade Reports: Non-SOM courses, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - MPPM to MBA conversion
    - General Information/Class Lists, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1978, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1979, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1980, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1981, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1982, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1983, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1984, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1985, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1986, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1987, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1988, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1989, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1990, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1991, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1992, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1993, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1994, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1995, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1996 A - L, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1996 M - Z, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1997 A - L, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1997 M - Z, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1998 A - L, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Alumni Forms, Class of 1998 M - Z, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Student ID numbers
    - Class of 1978, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Class of 1979, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Class of 1980, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Class of 1981, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Class of 1982, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Class of 1983, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Class of 1984, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Class of 1985, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Class of 1986, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Class of 1987, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Class of 1988, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Class of 1989, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Class of 1990, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Class of 1991, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Class of 1992, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Class of 1993, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Class of 1994, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Class of 1995, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Class of 1996, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Class of 1997, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Class of 1998, 1998 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 166)
- Registrar's notebooks, 1976-2009; Accession 2014-A-024
  Restricted until January 1, 2084
  The Registrar's notebooks consist academic calendars, course information and schedules, enrollment and tuition data, class/student lists (including non-SOM students), grade and degree requirements, diploma lists, and commencement records. Additional records are listed below in notes with the individual notebooks.
  Arrangement
  The Registrar's notebooks are arranged chonologically by academic year (Fall-Spring).
  - 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2A)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Also includes exam schedules, course preference questionnaires, and Outside and Special student reports.
  - 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Also includes faculty and staff list.
  - 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
    Also includes Joint Degree student files and faculty and staff directory.
  - 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    Also includes Preliminary Orientation Schedule.
  - 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
    Also includes Course Evaluation summaries.
  - 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 22-23)
  - 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 24-26)
  - 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
  - 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 29-30)
    Also includes academic policies records.
  - 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
  - 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 33-34)
    Also includes exam schedule.
  - 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 35-36)
  - 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 37-38)
    Also includes Enterprise Learning credits, financial aid records, Honor Code, International Experience files, exam schedule, Course Evaluation summaries, and Board of Advisor files.
  - 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 39-40)
- Admissions records, 2009-2012; Accession 2014-A-058
  Restricted until January 1, 2087
  - Class of 2009
  - Class of 2010
  - Class of 2011
  - Class of 2012
- Office of Financial Aid records, 1992-2014; Accession 2015-A-035
  Restricted until January 1, 2089
  - Administrative files
    - Declaration of finances, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Deutsche Bank loan program, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Gate student loan program
      - Gate loan packaging, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Portfolio performance status reports (PPSR), 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Portfolio performance status reports (PPSR), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Gate student loan program, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Homeland Security, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - International students
      - Class of 2004
        - Local contact information, 2004 Fall (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
        - Personal data forms, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10-14)
      - Class of 2005
        - Certification forms and contact information, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15-19)
      - Class of 2006
        - Certification forms and correspondence, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 20-24)
      - Class of 2008
        - Declararation of finances and correspondence, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Loan forgiveness-data and correspondence, 1992-2000 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
    - Master of Business Administration-Electronic (MBA-E)-Class of 2014, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Master of Advanced Management (MAM)-admissions and correspondence, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Monthly summary of payment reports, 1992-1998 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
    - Office of Institutional Research-reports and research data, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
    - Yale School of Management reports, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Student records
    - Class of 2002
    - Class of 2003
    - Class of 2004
    - Class of 2005
    - Class of 2006
    - Class of 2007
    - Class of 2009
    - Class of 2010
    - Class of 2011
    - Class of 2012
    - Class of 2013
    - Class of 2014
  - Student records MBA-E
    - Class of 2011
    - Class of 2012
    - Class of 2013
    - Class of 2014
- Records of Clayton P. Alderfer, 1969-1997; Accession 2016-A-059